435.890.9695 lia.bogoev@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/liabogoev

I'm a product manager who loves solving tough user problems. I believe technology is meant to help us, and I want to enable users to make the most of the tools they interact with. I research thoroughly and am passionate about data, but understand there is a human element beyond the metrics.

Experience

athenahealth Watertown, MA

Product Owner, Development Tools

Jan 2019 - present

- ▶ Performed first ever comprehensive analysis of user base (internal developers) through surveys and one-on-one user interviews, and used results to establish new strategy for the next 6 months.
- ▶ Spearheaded the organization of internal technology conference to train developers on best practices.

Senior Associate, Product Education

Jan 2018 - Jan 2019

Worked in a unique role on the team as a product owner of in-app training

- Created beta in-app training workflow to support the launch of a newly-redesigned critical page in athenaNet (27k daily average users), increased feature adoption by 37%.
- ▶ Developed 6-12 month product roadmap & launch strategy for in-app training on mobile & desktop.
- ▶ Streamlined in-app training creation process using WalkMe and developed internal training tools and support for a team of 13 instructional designers.

Associate, Product Education

Jan 2017 - Jan 2018

- ▶ Implemented a process to rapidly develop animations for eLearning materials, which improved content quality with no impact on development time. Trained 13 team members on new process.
- ▶ Redesigned and developed landing page for learning portal, enabling maintenance without the use of Photoshop. This ensured courses were listed as soon as available, and increased engagement by 10%.

Instructional Design Intern, Product Education

May 2016 - Dec 2016

▶ Created workflow video demo of new release features, which featured prominently in the fall 2016 release training materials.

MIT Information Systems & Technology

Cambridge, MA

Help Desk Consultant

Jan 2015 - May 2016

Created marketing and training videos for student outreach to increase awareness of services offered.

Education

Massachusetts Institute of Technology

January 2017

S.B. Architecture Studies, Comparative Media Studies focus

Relevant Coursework

- ▶ Product Institute Product Management
- ▶ Statistics—Designing Experiments
- ▶ Media Lab—Designing Interactions

- ▶ Game Design for Education
- ▶ Algorithms & Data Structure
- ▶ Operating Systems & Concurrency

Skills & More

- Scrum Alliance Certified Scrum Product Owner (CSPO)
- ▶ Adobe CC Suite, XD, Captivate

- ▶ Camtasia, WalkMe
- ▶ Fluent: HTML, CSS
- ▶ Familiar: SQL, Python, Java, jQuery, C++